&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么我们如何改进呢？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
how do we improve that?
我们必须测量。
We have to measure.
我没有必要做这个性能优化。
There's no point like I'm gonna
do this performance optimization.
你怎么知道A它起作用了还是B你实际上没有放慢速度，对吗？
How do you know that A it worked or B you
didn't actually slow things down, right?
因为如果你不知道自己在做什么，这有时是可能的。
Cuz that is sometimes possible if you
don't actually know what you're doing.
所以我们总是想先测量一下。
So we always want to measure first.
这是Rob Pike的一句话，这是Measure。
This is a quote from Rob Pike,
which is measure.
在测量之前不要调整速度，并且
Don't tune for
speed until you've measured, and
即使这样，除非其中一部分压倒了其余的部分，否则不要这样做。
even then don't unless one
part overwhelms the rest.
从第一页开始很容易，而且存在性能瓶颈，但是
It's easy to start with the first page,
and there's a performance bottle neck, but
这可能不是最重要的。
it might not be the most important one.
有一个叫做Skylight的应用程序，它是Rails性能监控
There's this application called Skylight,
which is rails performance monitoring
东西，它所做的就是根据痛苦对东西进行评级。
thing, and
what it does is it rates stuff by agony.
痛苦度量是页面有多慢，
The agony metric is how slow that page is,
乘以访问该页面的人数。
multiplied by how many
people visit that page.
因此，如果您的服务条款页面加载缓慢，
So if your terms of service
page is slow to load,
这是你应该对主页进行优化的第一件事吗？
is that the first thing you
should optimize vs the home page?
主页可能不会是。
The home page probably won't be.
就像是主页，它获得了所有的流量与服务条款
Like yeah the home page which gets all
this traffic versus the terms of service
没人读对吗？
which nobody reads right?
你应该喜欢优化那些比较重要的事情，然后从那里开始。
You should like optimize the things that
are kind of important and start there.
所以，是的，我们不想盲目地去，就像你可以看到这个，然后去，就像我知道
So yeah we don't wanna go just blindly
like you can see this and go like I know
所有这些事情，现在我要去，然后实现它，我的应用程序，但喜欢。
all these things now I'm gonna go and
then implement it my application but like.
我们想确保我们知道发生了什么，因为每个
We want to make sure we know
what's happening because every
抽象有某种取舍。
abstraction has some kind of trade-off.
我们将在今天的课程中看到一些东西，就像Chrome团队
We'll see things in this course today
where it's like the Chrome team
实现了这一特性，以便在大多数情况下使事情更快，但是
implemented this one feature to make
things faster most of the time, but
事实证明，有些时候它会让一些事情变得更慢。
it turns out that some of the time
it makes some of the things slower.
除非你在测量，否则你无法知道这一点。
Unless you're measuring you're
gonna have no way of knowing that.
你可能会对你的应用程序做一件坏事，
And you could be doing quote unquote
a bad thing to your application,
以做好事的名义，对吗？
in the name of doing a good thing, right?
所以测量很重要，因为就像，
So it's important to measure because like,
是的，它真的很容易看到你的应用程序上的下一个拉请求，而且
yeah, it gets really like easy to see the
very next pull request on your app, and
就像你在博客上读到的关于表现的建议一样，
start like dispensing advice that you
read on a blog post about performance,
当我们实际上没有任何真正的数据可以谈论的时候。
when we don't actually have
any real data to talk about.
这是我认为我们确实需要定期寻找的事情之一
And it is one of those things where I do
think we do need to regularly be looking
因为如果我们不是，是的，
at performance,
because if we're not, yeah,
是的，它足够快，直到它不是，然后它通常不是一个大的
yeah it's fast enough, until it's not,
and then it's usually not one big
性能问题是你的问题，但这就像千刀之死。
performance thing that is your problem,
but it's like death by a thousand cuts.
这是一千件事情，花费的时间大约是它们应有时间的两倍，
It's a thousand things that take
about twice as long as they should,
这最终会将您的应用程序搞得一团糟，我可以证明这一点。
that end up bringing your application
to a crawl and I can testify to that.
所以，只是有一些事情需要考虑。
So, just some things to think about.
我们是在测试花哨的Macbook Pro还是消费级硬件？
Are we testing on fancy Macbook Pros or
consumer grade hardware?
我们是否模拟了不完美的网络条件？
Are we simulating less than
perfect network conditions?
我们将讨论一下wi-fi实际上有多慢是非常糟糕的
We'll talk a little bit about how slow
wi-fi is actually phenomenally worse
比喜欢或不一致的WiFi甚至比一致的慢WiFi更糟糕，
than like or inconsistent WiFi is even
worst than a consistent slow WiFi,
但是，即使是对用户来说，缓慢的WiFi也只是普通的。
but slow WiFi even for
users is just general.
我宁愿没有WiFi也不愿使用慢WiFi。
I'd rather have no WiFi than slow WiFi.
我宁愿没事，没有互联网，我要读一本书。
I'd rather be okay, there's no Internet,
I'm gonna read a book.
我可以看到时间线正在加载。
I can see the timeline loading.
就像不酷一样。
Like not cool.
然后最后考虑绩效预算。
And then finally thinking
about performance budgets.
我认为这是一种非常有用的技术，
I think this is a really
useful technique of like,
这是我们的应用程序的状态。
this is the state of our application.
我们不希望它变得这么慢。
We don't want it to get this much slower.
我们希望它能更快
We'd like it to get this much faster and
从那里开始，然后在你改进一些东西的时候设置那些新的预算。
starting there and then setting those
new budgets as you improve some stuff.
所以最后一件要考虑的事情是，测量不是免费的。
So the one last thing to think about is,
measuring is not free.
我会把一堆控制台日志放在我的应用程序中，他们会记录时间
I'm gonna put a bunch of console logs in
my application, they're gonna log the time
除了那些控制台日志之外的每一秒都需要执行，对吗？
every second except those console
logs need to execute, right?
而你正在通过查看它来减慢你的应用程序的速度。
And you are slowing down
your app by looking at it.
这是另一种需要记住的重要事情，
And that's another kind of
important thing to keep in mind,
你可以把所有这些报告矩阵放在任何地方。
is you can put all these
reporting matrix everywhere.
但是这样做也会减慢应用程序的速度，所以
But you will also slow down
the application by doing that, so
别得意忘形。
don't get carried away.
最后一条建议是，很多这些东西会考虑什么
And one final piece of advice is a lot of
this stuff is gonna is thinking about what
我们称之为微观优化。
we call micro-optimizations.
这些小小的东西，我们会得到这个按钮，只是去一点点
These tiny little things we would get
the this button to go just a little bit
快点，对。
faster, right.
在我们有前端大师的国家管理课程中，我们谈了一点
In the state management course that we
have on Front End Masters we talk a little
有点关于这样一个事实，有时仅仅是你存储数据的方式和
bit about the fact that sometimes
just the way you store your data and
不是做一堆疯狂的事情。
not doing a bunch of crazy stuff.
而且您构建应用程序本身的方式可以让事情变得更快
And the way you architect the application,
itself, can make stuff faster
甚至在您担心实际的部件和编译性能之前。
before you even worry about the actual
parts and compilation performance.
有时它就像，嘿，你真的有一个页面上有1000行的表。
Sometimes it's like, hey, you actually
have a table with 1000 rows on the page.
在DOM中拥有所有这些行是很慢的。
And having all those
rows in the DOM is slow.
如果只是添加分页呢？
What if you just added pagination?
有时候，答案并不是我们今天要讨论的一些东西。
Sometimes the answer is not some of
the stuff we're going to talk about today.
我现在想做那个免责声明。
I want to make that disclaimer now.
有时只考虑应用程序的设计，
Sometimes just thinking about
the design of your application,
在应用程序中管理状态的方式。
the way you manage the state
in your application.
没有一颗银弹可以解决你所有的性能问题，
There's not one silver bullet that's going
to solve all your performance problems,
这就是为什么我们都能拿到钱，对吧。
which is why we all get paid Money, right.
因为如果是一个简单的方法，只要应用这个规则，我们就会让计算机来做，对吧。
Cuz if was an easy, just apply this rule,
we'd have computers do it, right.
我们可以自动化到没有批判性思维的程度
Everything that we can automate to the
point where there's no critical thinking
关于它，我们已经加入了算法，这就是那些
about it, we have put into algorithms,
and that's how the ones and
零来了，错误进入我的电脑，让事情发生。
zeroes that come over, the error
into my computer, make stuff happen.
好吧。
All right.
我们最后的免责声明是有三个层次的建议，
Final disclaimer as we go through this
is that there are three tiers of advice,
一定要这么做。
definitely do this.
也许这样做，但测量之前和之后。
Maybe do this, but
measure before and after.
只有当你有需要解决的问题时才这样做，对吧？
And only do this if you have
a problem that needs solving, right?
因此，我们使用这些作为我们的三个基准，因为我们谈论不同的
And so, we kind of use these as our three
benchmarks as we talk about different
技术，因为我再说一遍，今天我要说100遍。
techniques cuz again I'll say this,
I'm going to say this 100 times today.
有些事情可能会使您的应用程序在某些情况下变得更快，在另一些情况下变得更慢。
Some things might make your application
faster in some cases or slower in another.
就像，除非你知道问题是什么，否则你不知道会发生什么。
And like, unless you know what the problem
is, you don't know what's going to happen.
现在，我很高兴向你们展示这门课程的TLDR，
Now, I'm happy to unveil to you,
the TLDR of this course,
这是我的两条金科玉律。
which are my two golden
rules of performance.
你们都准备好了吗？
Are you all prepared for this?
第一条，做的事情越少，花的时间就越少。
Rule number one,
doing less stuff takes less time.
[笑]你笑，但就像字面上说的，
[LAUGH] You laugh but like literally,
[笑]这就是我们今天所做的，就像我们怎么做更少的东西？
[LAUGH] this is all we're doing today,
is like how do we do less stuff?
因为任何时候你做的东西越少，速度就越快。
Cuz anytime you do less stuff it's faster.
不做某事比做某事快得多。
Not doing something is way
faster than doing something.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：酷。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool.
我毁了这张幻灯片。
I ruined this slide.
我们会继续的。
We'll go on.
[笑]对于第二个，有人会争辩说，这是一个[INAUDIBLE]
[LAUGH] To the second one which is,
one would argue, this is a [INAUDIBLE] to
第一个，那就是，以后做事情比现在做好。
the first one, which is, doing stuff
later is better than doing it now.
对吧？但以后再做，
Right?
But doing it later,
你现在不能这么做。
you're not doing it now.
还有什么比做事情更快？
And what's faster than doing stuff?
什么都不做。
Not doing stuff.
所以，当你有疑问的时候，如果你可以不去做，那就不要去做。
So, when in doubt, if you can get
away with not doing it, don't do it.
如果你必须做这件事，你可以以后再做，以后再做。
If you have to do it and
you can do it later, do it later.
有人会认为这是绩效建议，
One would argue this
is performance advice,
另一个人可能会认为这是生活建议。
another person might argue
this is life advice.
我让你来评判这件事。
I'll let you be the judge of that.
我不打算走这条路，但对于网络性能来说，这绝对是真的。
I'm not going to go down that road but
it's definitely true for web performance.
好的，今天的大致轮廓。
All right, rough outline of the day.
谈谈JavaScript性能。
Talk about JavaScript performance.
有人会争辩说，如果我们按照时间顺序来做这件事，我们就会
One would argue that if we were doing this
in chronological order we were going to
首先讨论负载性能，但是
talk about load performance first, but
我们不是按时间顺序来做这件事的。
we're not doing this in
chronological order.
我们按我的顺序来做，
We're doing this in my order,
这就是我们将要讨论的JavaScript性能。
which is we're going to talk
about JavaScript performance.
我们希望编写运行更快、更晚或根本不运行的代码，对吗？
We wanna write code that runs faster,
later, or not at all, right?
因为不做事更快。
Cuz not doing stuff is faster.
明白了，所以我们将讨论一下JavaScript是如何编译的。
Got it, so we'll talk a little bit
about how your JavaScript is compiled.
我们把这个文本文件发送到浏览器，然后呢？
We send this text file over
to the browser, then what?
我们将讨论一下那里发生的事情。
We'll talk a little bit
about what happens there.
因为如果你只用谷歌的JavaScript性能，一半的东西
Because if you just Google JavaScript
performance, half the stuff
在那些博客帖子是真的，当博客帖子被写的时候，不再是真的了。
in those blog posts was true when the blog
post was written, is not true anymore.
它可能会变得很难弄清楚什么是真的，
And it can become very difficult to
figure out like what actually is true,
什么不是真的。
what's not true.
在你的应用程序中什么是真的，什么在你的应用程序中不是真的，所以
What true in your application,
what's not true in your application, so
实际上，我们讨论的是JavaScript引擎的工作原理。
actually we talk about how
JavaScript engine works.
我们将具体查看V8。
We'll look at V8 in specific.
我们会看到你发送代码的整个过程。
We'll actually see how the entire
process of, you sent code.
页面上有代码，实际上是在引擎盖下发生的。
There is code on page,
actually happens under the hood.
我们会自己进行基准测试，并尝试优化和
And we'll actually benchmark it
ourselves and try to optimize and
取消优化，看看会发生什么。
unoptimize stuff and see what happens.
那么，好吧，我们已经运行了代码。
Then, okay, we've run code.
我们准备好构建应用程序了。
We're ready to build app.
我们需要考虑渲染性能。
We need to think about
rendering performance.
因为JavaScript代码，正如我前面所说的，并不存在于真空中。
Cuz that JavaScript code, as I said
earlier, does not exist in a vacuum.
它必须与。
It has to interact with the.
除非你只是在写代码，在他们的浏览器中挖掘比特币，而
Unless you're just writing code that's
mining Bitcoin in their browser while
他们正在做其他的事情，很可能你正在改变用户界面。
they're doing something else, likely
you are changing the user interface.
这其中有我们需要考虑的含义。
There are implications to that
that we need to think about.
最后，负载性能。
Lastly, load performance.
如果您没有将应用程序提供给用户，则其他两个应用程序是不相关的。
If you do not get the application to
the user, the other two are irrelevant.